that was before the camera goes off
never do it well those sitting there
trying to cry on my personal Facebook
page and there was something in me that
said I was supposed to do it here for
whatever reason and I'm learning to
listen to that voice because the energy
PS takes me in amazing ways and it's a
piece of my journey I want to share with
the world because it's a it's an amazing
gift to me but there's also the other
the other side of it like having health
issues and having limitations is a
benefit to me in some ways it has given
me the ability to create what I'm
creating it's given me the only option
like it left me with only one option to
create when I'm creating and creating a
world this thought I have this last week
which also stairs the way again feeling
how I'm feeling at the moment was that
how I describe myself as selfish and
selfless that like what I'm creating is
a world in which I'm not considered
broken where because everyone's able to
live within their limitations and with
their best life and deal with their
energy cycles and yes I'm on the far end
of the spectrum of having basically no
energy and have to figure out what time
of day my brain works better and I'm
able to do certain things and I have to
not overdo it and I have to like keep my
body will someone spend energy doing
that and learning what works and what
doesn't work for my body and there's
blessings and learnings there that I
would never have otherwise and there's
also the actual downside like the crappy
and part of it and living it often
authentically is to feel crappy
sometimes and today I just feel crappy I
feel I'm dealing with this car Fiasco
and these people are just been it's been
a big learning for less like six months
and these people have taken on finding
me a car but it's also taking six months
and I have their car and what a part of
that what they promised was to drive the
new car to me because it's like a
or Drive and after I picked up the car I
currently have which I've had for five
months I think four months um he's been
going up for a while and they because I
was panicking and my friend was going
back from at leave and she was wanting
to drive me out there and she's back at
work now but they had promised that
they're gonna drive it to me and he was
like oh actually a - back at work so
you're can you drive up here you can say
you're gonna need to but could you
possibly drive out here I'm like no no I
can't
it's now November it's rainy I
definitely can't drive but even driving
with someone with these like I just I
can't have a lot anxiety of going out
there and in my body I don't know like
I'm dealing with this feeling of knowing
that that's the boundary I have to send
for my own health because allowing
myself stress in my body allowing myself
to get cold it means that I'm spending
energy that I don't have and I can't
like I'm still recovering from summer
and it being hot it's November and that
piece sucks I think I'm not doing as
well as I would like to but I'm also not
taking care of myself as well as I could
be but also can't be like I have to
accept where I am and I only have so
many spoons and I only have the ability
to do so many things none of which
involve working full time but they do
involve my world-changing project
because it's worth it deciding spoons on
and I'm just sitting here anyway
and it's the automatic it's the flow
it's not forcing it in any way which is
stressful in its own way and it's a
stress I think people do and should
allow but I can't I can't have that
stress of like no you need to sit in you
need to do this you need it doesn't work
it exhausts my body my body does not
have a great stress response after brain
surgery
brain damage resulting from it and
radiation it just doesn't do the best
with it
it's neurologically hurt like it makes
sense to me but sharing that peace that
it does sometimes I'm clearly not
in tears
I wasn't over there and something told
me to come on here and that has been
because the surrender to the not having
stress in my life and having to reassess
what everything he basically means to me
has been the greatest gift that I want
to be able to help other people tap into
and just like the project where I fall
short is in the communication of it and
being able to express it but even if I'm
not perfect to that I do so much better
when I just go with the flow and allow
it which is what I do do when I'm doing
this by myself you know he no one's ever
gonna see it versus being on here if I
knew the difference if I could just be
the other thing I would but I it's
different it feels different and I have
to figure out the feeling of my body and
help recreate it as opposed to making it
be different than what it is I feel a
little better
because I do feel like I'm exactly where
I'm supposed to be and maybe this will
help someone maybe someone else is going
through anxiety neurological and I
don't know everyone say it gets better
you get you get better at it not getting
better
anyway